Colette Parker

Berlin Metropolitan Area



colette.parker91@outlook.com



linkedin.com/in/colettejoyparker

Summary

I'm a full stack web developer with a background in digital healthcare. I transitioned to software development because of my understanding of user experience and strong sense of curiosity that makes me want to develop my own technical solutions. Recent roles in medical startups have satisfied my desire to develop products that are helpful in customers day to day life. I am currently working on an Angular project building a client side for my marvel movies application based on my existing server side code (REST API and database). My key skills include:

Patient experience knowledge Project management Understanding GDPR regulations in a healthcare setting **Cross Team Collaboration** Data analysis HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, MongoDB, PostgreSQL

Experience



🐚 Senior Health Manager

Qunomedical GmbH

Sep 2017 - Feb 2022 (4 years 6 months)

B2C patient management role with direct communication with clinics and hospitals.

Working on training sessions and point of call for other team members on multiple treatment specialties. Able to provide basic information on all treatment specialities with a focus on more complicated and multi modal treatments for patients.

Attending all treatment and general training sessions. Being a key member on the program with the German Accelerator. Communicating with several different internal departments to improve processes, and knowledge sharing.

Sales Consultant

Watchmaster

Nov 2016 - Aug 2017 (10 months)

B2C role. My focus was both on sales and inbounding watches. Responsible for UK customers and the market. Providing efficient and helpful information to customers to help with their purchase or sale. Designated in-house information source for questions on our financing system. Developing and providing training to newer employees. Successfully reaching quotas of over £200,000 GMV in a month.

Education



CareerFoundry

Full-Stack Immersion

Apr 2022 - Oct 2022
Javascript
Server-side programming and Node.js
Client side programming and React
Testing in the development process
Native app development and React Native
Angular
Collaboration and Documentation

CF CareerFoundry

Singer.

Intro to Front End Development
Apr 2022 - Apr 2022
HTML
CSS
Git and version control
Code Quality, Testing, and Web Hosting

Birmingham City University

BA (hons), English Literature 2011 - 2015

Studying an extensive set of modules that include the philosophy of art, contemporary moral and social philosophy and gender, sex and culture in literature. Providing critic essay's and critical presentations. Studying etymology and the development of children's language in modules but also continuing research into those fields outside of the set assessments. Learning to provide strong arguments and the criticisms of them, in a comparative setting. Studying philosophers including Kant, Collingwood and

As an optional module I studied Spanish.

North Warwickshire and Hinckley College

Level 3 Award, Leadership and Management 2014 - 2014

Licenses & Certifications

Perioperative Medicine in Action - UCL https://www.futurelearn.com/certificates/7yd88w9

Hospital Operations: Improving Patient Experience - Deakin University

https://www.futurelearn.com/certificates/bpnenp1

Management and Leadership: Well-being and welfare at work - The Open

University Business School

https://www.futurelearn.com/certificates/mzsy942

Protecting Health Data in the Modern Age: Getting to Grips with the GDPR -

University of Groningen, Faculty of Law

https://www.futurelearn.com/certificates/9lmqkhh

Mangement and Leadership: Leading a Team - The Open University Business School

https://www.futurelearn.com/certificates/sc3wt07

Effective Questioning for Call Handlers - University of East Anglia

https://www.futurelearn.com/certificates/0yt588m

People Management Skills - CIPD

https://www.futurelearn.com/certificates/v0uenix

📆 Digital health for Cancer Management: Smart Health Technologies in Complex

Diseases - Taipei Medical University

https://www.futurelearn.com/certificates/24toccl

Basic First Aid - University of Glasgow

https://www.futurelearn.com/certificates/dzrhagh

An Introduction to Medical Ethics: The Impact of Disability Screening - The

University of Manchester

https://www.futurelearn.com/certificates/jjc5w89

MedTech: Orthopaedic Implants and Regenerative Medicine - University of Leeds

https://www.futurelearn.com/certificates/9pwh5os

The NHS Explained: How the Health System in England Really Works - The King's Fund

https://www.futurelearn.com/certificates/ai9njpk

Healthcare Research: For Healthcare Professionals - Coventry University

https://www.futurelearn.com/certificates/qtisdgo

Implementing Innovation in Healthcare - Monash University

https://www.futurelearn.com/certificates/9d6zpy6

Skills

Customer Service • Research • Social Media • Customer Satisfaction • Retail Sales • Social Networking • E-Learning • Makaton • PowerPoint • Learning Quickly

Honors & Awards

Student of the Year - North Warwickshire and Hinckley College

Jul 2007

Student of the year at NWHC for GCSE Law.

Finalist - Warwickshire Schools Debating Competition

Jul 2007

Winning the finals of the Warwickshire Schools Debating Competition.

Achievement award - Manor Park Community School

Jun 2004

Achievement award in the creative arts.

UK Intermediate Mathematical Challenge - Bronze Certificate - UK Intermediate Mathematical Challenge
Jun 2004

UK Intermediate Mathematical Challenge - Silver certificate - UK Intermediate Mathematical Challenge Jun 2005

UK Intermediate Mathematical Challenge - Silver certificate - UK Intermediate Mathematical Challenge Jun 2007

UK Intermediate Mathematical Challenge - Silver certificate - UK Intermediate Mathematical Challenge Jun 2008

Good Brain, Bad Brain - FutureLearn

Aug 2020

Completion of the full program consisting of 3 courses.

By completing the program, I am able to:

- describe the key features of the cells that make up the human nervous system that allow them to carry out their function;
- explain how the arrangement of these cells within the human brain relates to brain function; describe the defining symptoms of Parkinson's disease and explain how the pathology seen in Parkinson's disease leads to these symptoms;
- explain the rationale behind the currently used treatments for Parkinson's disease;

- appreciate the need for new therapies and what our increasing understanding of the neurobiology is telling us about what possible new therapies there might be;
- describe the stages of drug discovery and development, from scientists having the first idea to it being used in clinical treatment.